(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-20T18:15:36.768404",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
hololive SUPER EXPO 2023 デジタルメッセージボード
[hololive SUPER EXPO 2023 Digital Message Board]
hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade DAY 2
グッズラインナップ紹介
[Goods Lineup Introduction]
商品ラインナップ！
[Product Lineup!]
OFFICIAL ITEMS
PENLIGHT COLORS
デジタルメッセージボード
[Digital Message Board]
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiss Schwarz!
ホロライブプロダクションがまたまたカードに大集合！
Hololive Production is coming together in cards once again!
広がるヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
The expanding world of Weiss Schwarz!
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション ボリューム2！
Booster Pack: Hololive Production Vol. 2!
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
春来いもうすぐでバイバイ まわるぎるたびふあけ
Spring's almost here, bye-bye, every time I spin...
なんて 病んで みた の (笑) そう言えば もうすぐ…
Or so I pretended to be sick (lol) Come to think of it, soon...
春一番 が 吹い て キミ に 会える もう 怖い ない よ ポカポカ
The first spring storm will blow, and I can see you, no longer scared, so warm.
How you ever smile? Now we're pushing somehow
グッズ ラインナップ 紹介
Goods Lineup Introduction
商品ラインナップ！
Product Lineup!
ホロスターズ グッズ
Holostars Goods
hololive production Art Collection
ホロライブ 事務所グッズ
Hololive Office Goods
HOLOLIVE ALTERNATIVE グッズ
Hololive Alternative Goods
マンガート ビームス コラボグッズ
Mangart Beams Collab Goods
holo*27 コラボグッズ
holo*27 Collab Goods
BUSHIROAD グッズ
Bushiroad Goods
GOOD SMILE COMPANY グッズ
Good Smile Company Goods
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiß Schwarz!
ホロライブプロダクションが、まだまだカードに大集合！
Hololive Production is coming to cards in a big way once again!
広がるヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Expanding Weiß Schwarz!
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション Vol.2
Booster Pack Hololive Production Vol.2
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
舶来モチで バイバイ
Bye-bye with imported mochi
サイマル起きてぬるりつかえ
Waking up simultaneously, slipping and getting stuck
だって全開やになっちゃってもやめていたくて
Because even if I go full throttle and get sick of it, I want to keep going...
どうしちゃったの 絶対好きでしょ
What's wrong with you? You definitely like it, right?
Are you embarrassed right now or blushing somehow?
Our Bright Parade PENLIGHT COLORS
hololive SUPER EXPO 2023 DIGITAL MESSAGE BOARD
hololive SUPER EXPO 2023 デジタルメッセージボード
[hololive SUPER EXPO 2023 Digital Message Board]
hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade DAY 2
hololive SUPER EXPO 2023 グッズ ラインナップ
[hololive SUPER EXPO 2023 Goods Lineup]
商品ラインナップ！
[Product Lineup!]
ホロスターズ ミニキャラアクリルキーホルダー
[HOLOSTARS Mini Character Acrylic Keyholder]
hololive production Art Collection
ホロライブ 事務所グッズ
[hololive Office Goods]
HOLOLIVE ALTERNATIVE グッズ
[HOLOLIVE ALTERNATIVE Goods]
マンガート ビームス コラボグッズ
[MANGART BEAMS Collaboration Goods]
holo*27 コラボグッズ
[holo*27 Collaboration Goods]
BUSHIROAD グッズ
[BUSHIROAD Goods]
GOOD SMILE COMPANY グッズ
[GOOD SMILE COMPANY Goods]
Our Bright Parade OFFICIAL ITEMS
Our Bright Parade PENLIGHT COLORS
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ
Weiß Schwarz
ホロライブプロダクションが またまたカードに大集合！
Hololive Production is coming together in cards once again!
広がるヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Expanding Weiß Schwarz!
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション Vol.2
Booster Pack hololive production Vol.2
3月24日(金)発売
Available Friday, March 24!
ブシロード
Bushiroad
これでいいのだ 好好好
All's a-ok-o, ha-ha-hao
好みの需要と供給の寒暖差 また風邪っぴきさん
Love's supply and demand... You're sick again, poor thing
どうしちゃったの 好き好き絶対好きだけどさ
What's wrong? Love, love, absolutely love you, but...
I'll go embrace I'm now a-pushin' somehow
オイ！オイ！オイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey!
星街すいせい
Hoshimachi Suisei
アキ・ローゼンタール
Aki Rosenthal
白上フブキ
Shirakami Fubuki
夏色まつり
Natsuiro Matsuri
湊あくあ
Minato Aqua
紫咲シオン
Murasaki Shion
百鬼あやめ
Nakiri Ayame
大神ミオ
Ookami Mio
猫又おかゆ
Nekomata Okayu
戌神ころね
Inugami Korone
兎田ぺこら
Usada Pekora
宝鐘マリン
Houshou Marine
天音かなた
Amane Kanata
常闇トワ
Tokoyami Towa
雪花ラミィ
Yukihana Lamy
桃鈴ねね
Momosuzu Nene
獅白ぼたん
Shishiro Botan
ムーナ・ホシノヴァ
Moona Hoshinova
アーニャ・メルフィッサ
Anya Melfissa
パヴォリア・レイネ
Pavolia Reine
森カリオペ
Mori Calliope
がうる・ぐら
Gawr Gura
IRyS
セレス・ファウナ
Ceres Fauna
オーロ・クロニー
Ouro Kronii
ハコス・ベールズ
Hakos Baelz
Our Bright Parade
[Title: Our Bright Parade]
同じ未来を見ていたい
I want to see the same future,
あの夢を手に入れたい
I want to grasp that dream.
それぞれ違った心で
With each of our different hearts,
走り出そう
Let's start running!
どこを見ても眩ららな場所に目覚めてた
No matter where I looked, I awoke in a dazzling place,
ほんの小さなきみにこの瞳奪われた
My eyes were captivated by just a tiny you.
不安で揺れる心をうまくチューニングして
Tuning my heart that trembles with anxiety,
ほんの小さな
Just a tiny...
王 僕らの king world
Oh, our king world
アイノウ 僕らの true な 世界
I know, our true world
諦めの街で
In a town of resignation,
愛しいと進む
moving forward with affection,
苦しい時も
even through painful times,
もう私は ひとりじゃないから
because I'm no longer alone.
だからもっと夢を追いかけたい
That's why I want to chase my dreams even more,
ワクワクとまらない 鼓動を越えてく
beating with unstoppable excitement, transcending my heartbeat
世界に手を出してあげる
and reaching out to the world!
アクセスしてみたい
I want to try accessing it,
後悔なんてさせない それぞれ違った心で
never letting you regret it, with our own unique hearts,
走れよ
run!
青空に輝く 眩しい想いは
The dazzling feelings shining in the blue sky
見たことのない光を
are lights I've never seen before,
リアルに届けるよ
delivered to reality.
いつも聞こえるエールは ここにキャプチャして
Always capturing the cheers I hear right here,
また新しい光を探したくなるよ
making me want to search for a new light once again.
君の笑顔は
Your smile
奔走して進む
rushing forward as I go,
悲しい時に振り返るよ
looking back on sad times.
汐風が吹くから
because the sea breeze blows!
胸を張って夢を追いかけたい 奇跡のストーリー
Standing tall and chasing my dreams in this miraculous story,
一緒につくろう 終わらない夢を 誰ひとり欠かせない
let's create together an endless dream where no one is left behind.
愛が重なるこの世界 それぞれ違った心で
In this world where our love overlaps, with our own unique hearts,
色飾れ
let's color it!
悲しい時も 寂しい時も
Even in sad times, even in lonely times,
気持ち信じ合えるものがある 忘れずにこの頃を
there is something we can believe in together—never forgetting these days,
鳴らし続けたい 終わらない世界に
I want to keep ringing them out into this endless world,
溢れ出すよ 笑顔たち
overflowing with our smiles!
憧れの舞台たち らししく輝きたい
On the stage of our dreams, I want to shine like myself.
時に涙して また笑い合いたい
Sometimes shedding tears, yet wanting to laugh together again.
同じ未来も見たい あの夢手にしたい
I want to see that same future, I want to hold that dream in my hands.
踏み出すぞ 奇跡の 一歩を
Step forward, take that miraculous step!
息切らして夢を追いかけたい
Catching my breath, I want to chase my dreams,
ワクワクとまらない
with unstoppable excitement,
鼓動を越えてく 世界に手を出してあげる
transcending my heartbeat and reaching out to the world!
アクセスしてみたい
I want to try accessing it,
後悔なんてここにない それぞれ違った心で
with a unique heart, with no regrets whatsoever.
作ろう
Let's create it!
そう、お待たせいたしました！
Yes, thank you for waiting!
ここからはスーパー白上タイム 略してSSCのお出ましだー！
From here on is Super Shirakami Corn time, abbreviated as SSC!
ここ狐？
A fox here?
私は白上フブキです！
I am Shirakami Fubuki!
お歌と踊りとゲームが大好きオタクのバーチャル狐です！
A virtual fox otaku who loves singing, dancing, and gaming!
いろんなことして狭まいに楽しく活動してるのでふぶちゃんフブキ白上皆さんお好きに呼んでください！
I'm active in all sorts of fun ways, so please feel free to call me Fubuki-chan, Fubuki, Shirakami, whatever you like!
今日が初めての人も
To those experiencing this for the first time today,
いつも観てくれてる人も
and those who always watch me,
一人一人の力で私はここにいます！
I am here thanks to the power of each and every one of you!
そう今日もずっと変わらないこの場所で
Yes, even today, in this unchanging place,
君に1対手を差し伸べて
I'll reach out my hand to you one-on-one,
まだまだ見ぬ世界中
into a world we haven't seen yet.
川渡したくすぎる日々は宝物ですよ
Days rushing by so fast are truly treasures!
泣いたって寄り添ってたいすぐ隣
Even if you cry, I want to stay close by your side,
笑顔で一緒にハイハイそうこころをふたり重ねて届け
smiling together, stacking our hearts and delivering it to you!
ほーっと ひと息 お茶 ですよ (はい、どーぞ!)
Take a breath, it's tea time! (Here you go!)
いつもの 場所 から 元気 にせーの で ご挨拶
Greeting everyone cheerfully from our usual place!
おっはこーん ですよー!
Good morning-con!
始めましょう!
Let's get started!
おしゃべり をして ゲーム と 過ごす そんな 毎 日 が 愛しく て
Chatting and playing games, everyday life is so dear...
あれも これも 手 を 出し たく なり がち です
I tend to want to try everything out.
歌 とか ステージ は まだまだ 恥ずかしい けど
Singing and stages are still a bit embarrassing, but...
支え 合って ほら 届け ます よ この 声 を
Supporting each other, look, I'll deliver this voice to you!
say! ほら その 顔 上げ て みんなで 手 を 取れ ば
Say! Look, lift your face up, if we all take hands...
dive! まだまだ 道 の 途中 世界 を 越え よう
Dive! We're still on the way, let's cross the world!
say! ほら 推し お 仕事 も 止まら ない 全力 です から!
Say! Look, even oshi work doesn't stop, because I'm giving my all!
夢 を 書き かえ たら 追いかけ 続け よう
Once we rewrite our dreams, let's keep chasing them!
ともに (はい!) つなぐ (はい!) ファンファレ (GO!)
Together (Yes!), connected (Yes!), fanfare (GO!)
ちょーっと やわかした 時 でも (もう 大丈夫!)
Even when things got a bit soft... (It's alright!)
気持ち 切り替え て ぼーっ と し ちゃう 昼下がり は ひるこーん です よー!
Resetting our mood in the lazy afternoon, it's afternoon-con!
背伸び をして お腹 へっ たら すぐ モグモグ と お茶 の 間食
Stretching up, when hungry, munching right away on afternoon snacks.
黒い あのコ には 内緒 に して 欲しい です
Please keep it a secret from that black cat.
仲間 の 力 と お友達 の みなさん と 叶え たい 思い は 言葉 にして 一つ 一つ
With the power of companions and all my friends, turning the feelings I want to grant into words one by one.
say! ほら その 手 上げ て みんなで 輪 に なれ ば
Say! Look, raise that hand, if we all form a circle...
dive! まだまだ 成長 途中 問題 ない でしょ?
Dive! We're still growing, no problem, right?
say! ほら 明るく 元気 な 心 が 取り柄 です から!
Say! Look, a bright, cheerful heart is my strong suit!
へこみ がち な とき も 輝き 続け よう
Even when feeling low, let's keep shining on!
ともに (はい!) つなぐ (はい!) アンコール (GO!)
Together (Yes!), connected (Yes!), encore (GO!)
なにもかもが 新しくて 右も左も わからない とき も
When everything was brand new and I didn't know which way was up...
がんばれ た の は 一人 じゃない から
I was able to do my best because I wasn't alone.
一つ 一つ 応援 が 後押し になって 一歩 ずつ でも
Every single cheering voice pushed me forward, step by step...
わたし は 自分らしく 磨いて いく フューチャー
I'll polish my own future true to myself.
答え も イメージ も まだまだ 手探り でも 響き 合って ほら 世界 は 今 色めいて
Even while groping for answers and images, resonating together, look, the world is vibrant now!
say! さあ その 顔 上げ て みんなで 手 を 取れ ば
Say! Now, lift your face up, if we all take hands...
dive! これから 夢 の 先 へ 駆け出そ う
Dive! Let's dash forth beyond the dream!
say! ほら 推し お 仕事 も 止まら ない 全力 です から!
Say! Look, even oshi work never stops, because I'm giving my all!
大好き な 思い が あふれ そう な ほど
To the point where my immense affection is overflowing.
ともに (はい!) つなぐ (はい!) ファンファレ (GO!)
Together (Yes!), connected (Yes!), fanfare (GO!)
ここまで よく できました!
You did a great job getting this far!
最後に 一つ!
One last thing!
三千 回じゃ 足り ない ぞ? 100万 回 愛し てる!
Three thousand times isn't enough? I love you a million times!
これまで を 支えて くれた みんなに 寄り添いたい なって
I wanted to stay close to everyone who has supported me thus far.
大切な 仲間たち と これからも 今も ずっと 大好きな この 場所 で
With my precious companions, now and always in this beloved place.
君 も 一体って 押したって ウェルカム ぺい! ワクワク ドキシン中
You too, sing along, push along, welcome, hey! Excited and pounding with joy.
まだまだ 明日 も 未来 も 音頭 も 鳴らして いこう
Tomorrow and the future too, let's keep playing the ondo!
泣いてだって 叫んでだって 大好き! えがお で 一緒 に ハイ! ファイ! ポーズ!
Even if we cry or shout, I love you! Together with a smile, high-five pose!
心 を 二人 重ねて 届けましょう!
Let's bring our hearts together and deliver it!
泣いてだって 叫んでだって 大好き! えがお で 一緒 に ハイ! ファイ! ポーズ!
Even if we cry or shout, I love you! Together with a smile, high-five pose!
心 を ふたり 重ねて 届け ましょう!
Let's bring our hearts together and deliver it!
楽しい 時間 が みんな と ここ で 本当に 幸せ です!
Having such a fun time with everyone here, I'm truly happy!
ありがとう ございました!
Thank you very much!
hey! ha! hey! yo! yo!
さあ 新曲 を ひらめい たぞ! いーち! に! さーん! わん! つー! わん! つー! せーの!
Now, I've thought of a new song! One! Two! Three! One! Two! One! Two! Ready, go!
そんな ところ も かわいい よ?
Even places like that are cute, right?
みんな や お菓子 食べて こい こい!
Everyone, eat some sweets and come along!
共に ぼーっ として おい! おい!
Spacing out together, oi! oi!
好き を 歌え ば よい! よい!
Singing what you love, yoi! yoi!
でも ね 疲れたら ゆっくり と 歩み ましょう
But you know, if you're tired, let's take it nice and slow.
人生 なんて 気楽 に 考え ましょ
Let's take life easy and carefree.
なんて やせたら ちゃんと しろ 程度 どち どち どち
Saying things like "lose weight" or "act your age," step by step...
乱世 の 君 は 大 正解!
You in these chaotic times are absolute perfection!
だって この世 は めっちゃ かわいい! どんな 姿 だ とも なお かわいい!
Because this world is super cute! No matter what form you take, you're even cuter!
生まれてくれて ありがとう ね 大大大大大好き!
Thank you for being born into this world, I love you so, so, so much!
さまざま に ラブラブ だ から あまり 歩か ない よ 作ろ う
Since we're all wonderfully affectionate, let's not walk too much and make something.
あんまり 振り回し すぎたら ほっか し て あきらめ られ ちゃう ぞ
If you push me around too much, I might just get abandoned and given up on!
とどずに 出会い て ほしい な そんな ところ も かわいい よ?
I want us to keep meeting without end, even places like that are cute, right?
だって この世 は めっちゃ かわいい! どんな 姿 だ とも なお かわいい!
Because this world is super cute! No matter what form you take, you're even cuter!
心配 は 気 に し て なん ない! よっぽど 心配 に なっ て き た!
Don't worry about your worries at all! It's getting me all worried instead!
世界一？可愛い
World's most? Cute!
宇宙一？可愛い
Universe's most? Cute!
もっともっと聞かせて
Let me hear more and more
ご褒美は目を閉じて？
Is the reward closing your eyes?
ちゅっ
Chu!
見つけてくれてサンキュー
Thank you for finding me
愛してくれてサンキュー
Thank you for loving me
生き甲斐にしちゃってもいいのよ
It's okay to make me your reason to live
一人じゃ無理だ逆境
Adversity is impossible alone
みんながいれば最強
If everyone is together, we're the strongest
見詰め合って両想い
Staring at each other and falling in love
「好きになっちゃえ!」
"Fall in love with me!"
涙じゃ何も解決しないの分かってだから
I know that tears won't solve anything, so
だから“言葉で”“行動で”魅せるよ
That's why with words and actions I'll charm you
覚悟はいい?
Are you ready?
世界一？可愛い
World's most? Cute!
宇宙一？可愛い
Universe's most? Cute!
もっともっと声出しよそ見はダメ! ok?
Raise your voice more and more, no looking away! OK?
まばたきも？可愛い
Even blinking? Cute!
存在が？可愛い
Existence is? Cute!
もっともっと聞かせて
Let me hear more and more
ご褒美は目を閉じて？
Is the reward closing your eyes?
ちゅっ
Chu!
歌ってくれてサンキュー
Thank you for singing
笑顔をくれてサンキュー
Thank you for giving me a smile
生きててよかったって思った
I thought I'm glad I'm alive
ちょっとのミスは愛嬌だけどやる気は最強
A little mistake is charming, but motivation is strongest
競い合って高め合おう
Let's compete and lift each other up
せーので行こう!
On the count of, let's go!
“苦手”をずっと逃げちゃえば愛はだから
Running away from weaknesses means love won't reach
だから何度だって何度も挑戦を楽しんじゃおう!
That's why let's challenge over and over and enjoy it!
あざとくて？可愛い
Cunningly? Cute!
最高に？可愛い
Most? Cute!
私だけをロックオンよそ見はダメ! ok?
Lock on only to me, no looking away! OK?
寝起きでも？可愛い
Even right after waking up? Cute!
存在が？可愛い
Existence is? Cute!
ずっとずっと聞かせて輝くから
Let me hear on and on because I'll shine
「約束ね」
"It's a promise"
上手に出れてるかな?
Can I sing well?
上手におどれてるかな?
Can I dance well?
間違うの怖くなるけどできるできるできるできる
I get scared of making mistakes, I can, I can, I can, I can
そうだ!信じてくれる人がいるこの歌で君と繋がっていられる
That's right! There are people who believe in me, I can connect with you through this song
忘れられないストーリー描いていこういくーよ!
Let's draw an unforgettable story, here we go!
世界一？可愛い
World's most? Cute!
宇宙一？可愛い
Universe's most? Cute!
もっともっと声出しよそ見はダメ! ok?
Raise your voice more and more, no looking away! OK?
まばたきも？可愛い
Even blinking? Cute!
存在が？可愛い
Existence is? Cute!
もっともっと聞かせて
Let me hear more and more
ご褒美は目を閉じて？
Is the reward closing your eyes?
ちゅっ
Chu!
絶対お前がアニマル
You're definitely an animal!
なんて心臓撃ち抜くのさ
My heart is pierced!
超弩級だから最後まで耳の中こじ開けて聞けよ
Since it's super-dreadnought, keep your ears wide open and listen till the end!
行くよ
Here we go!
約束その1
Promise number 1:
私以外の女の子とは目を合わせないこと
Never make eye contact with other girls!
約束その2
Promise number 2:
破った場合電パルス火炙りか考えないものとする
If you break it, death by electric pulse or burning at the stake!
方針なんて曖昧だね
Such vague policies,
突然急死しちゃうぞ
You'll die of a sudden shock!
告白だって泣いたって許さない絶対許さない
Confessions or tears won't be forgiven, absolutely not!
だめっ！ふらふら浮気は
No! Faltering and cheating
許さないから
Will never be forgiven!
昔ような人には
To someone from the old days,
用件なんてあげないないない
I won't give any business at all!
メーデイーデーです
Mayday, Mayday,
絶対お前がアニマル
You're definitely an animal!
乱れ咲きちょっとビビるもぐしを捉えよなんと恋だわ
Blooming wildly, trembling a bit, capturing you, what a love this is!
このまま立ってファイヤア
Standing just like this, fire!
一番可愛いのは誰？
Who is the cutest?
祭り！
Matsuri!
もっともっとアニマル超弩級のドキ愛ワンツウ
More and more, animal super-dreadnought pounding love one-two!
絶対お前がアニマル超弩級のドキ愛ワンツウ
You're definitely an animal, super-dreadnought pounding love one-two!
約束その3
Promise number 3:
他の女に可愛いって言わないこと
Never call another girl cute!
約束その4
Promise number 4:
破ったら針千本飲ませて私釘付けの刑
If you break it, I'll make you swallow a thousand needles and nail you down!
崇拝だって純愛だってさ
Worship or pure love,
革命前夜ファンタジー
The eve of revolution fantasy!
王国だって開拓未来絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対許さない
Paving the way to the kingdom of the future, absolutely, absolutely never forgiven!
よりどりみどりね
Pick and choose as you like,
ステキよねオボッチャマ
Isn't it wonderful, young master?
一寸先も分かんないないない
You never know what's a fraction ahead!
やきもきです
I'm all jittery!
絶対お前始めちゃうわ
I'm definitely going to start with you,
君を狙ってきっちりなし一般教養
Targeting you precisely, standard education:
恋を先生勝ち取ったお祭りこと
winning love as festival master!
一番可愛いのは誰？
Who is the cutest?
祭り！
Matsuri!
もっともっとアニマル超弩級のドキ愛ワンツウ
More and more, animal super-dreadnought pounding love one-two!
絶対お前がアニマル超弩級のドキ愛ワンツウ
You're definitely an animal, super-dreadnought pounding love one-two!
まずいぞ
This is bad!
一番可愛いのは誰？
Who is the cutest?
祭り！
Matsuri!
よろしい！大好きだぞ
Excellent! I love you!
ねぇこんなこと言いたくないよ本当は
Hey, I really don't want to say things like this,
だけど本気で伝えておけばよかったなってさ
But I wish I had conveyed it seriously...
後悔したくないのね
I don't want to have any regrets,
分かって？我慢も愛
Understand? Patience is also love!
一番可愛いのは誰？
Who is the cutest?
祭り！
Matsuri!
絶対お前始めちゃうわ
I'm definitely going to start with you,
君を狙ってきっちりなし一般教養
Targeting you precisely, standard education!
もっともっとアニマル超弩級のドキ愛ワンツウ
More and more, animal super-dreadnought pounding love one-two!
絶対お前がアニマル
You're definitely an animal!
剥がれ落ちたメイク すっぴんのアニマル
The makeup peels off, a barefaced animal,
醜くてもやっちゃうのよ
I'll do it even if it's ugly.
おすわりとかできない だって待てできない
Can't sit, can't even stay,
喉鳴らして いっちゃうまで
purring until I go.
がぶっとしてよっか 高まるビート
Why don't you bite me? The accelerating beat,
良いも悪いも全然しよ
let's do both good and bad.
ハマってみよっか 突撃するゲート
Let's get hooked, charging through the gate,
愛に期待は禁物だよ
expecting love is strictly forbidden.
ねぇ止められないほどに狂いたい
Hey, I want to go crazy beyond stopping.
涙とどけ そして永遠の星へ
Delivering tears, and to the eternal stars,
最大級のななななななびー
Maximum grade na-na-na-na-na-na-bee!
みんな完璧そう
Everyone looks so flawless.
行けそう
We can make it.
最強ヴァルサイユにビビるのが大概の毎回だ
Getting scared of supreme Versailles is usually how it goes.
ワンツースリーで繋がった世界にアイが溢れ出す
Love overflows into a world connected by one, two, three.
8bitに感じるドキドキ 運命のラブじゃダメですか
The 8-bit heartbeat, is a fateful love not enough?
演算状態ふざけんな レベルアップして超えてやれ
Processing state, no kidding! Level up and surpass it!
夢に見てるファンファーレと ノイズ超えて
Beyond the fanfare I dream of and the noise,
生きていって個性いてってとか ソテガイはロマンスを語れ
outer guys talk about romance.
ナッピナッピ小さなビットにデッカイアイを監視中
Monitoring huge love in a tiny bit.
どこでももっとも許してね
Forgive me anywhere and everywhere.
浸ってアイは一国一城
Immersed in love, my own sovereign castle.
ジャンピングジャンピング跳ねるハート
Jumping, jumping, bounding heart!
システム回せおいせね ミントなんて終わらないで
Spin the system, don't let mint end.
続くエンドレスに眠るまで
Until I fall asleep in the endless continuation.
人生とかけて無理ゲーと解く どちらも釣り上がりがみえません
Comparing life to an impossible game, neither shows any sign of rising.
このラヴバウンド状態異常を解く アイテムはどこで買いました?
Where did you buy the item to cure this love-bound status abnormality?
したいをせめを足りないどこで 怒りなのは私のAINP!
What's making me angry is my AINP!
まぁどんな難所もこれでやるけど その前に誰か予定ありますか?
Well, I'll clear any difficult spot, but do you have plans?
ちゃんと届いてるあなたのエール
Your cheering is reaching me properly.
ひしいたのボスがめでたい 冷たい失敗も隠すの呪文
A spell to hide cold failures.
ナッピナッピ小さなビットでデッカイ世界良くし中
Improving the huge world with tiny bits.
うまくいかないプレイング 瞑想だってあなたとしたい
Playing that doesn't go well, I want to meditate with you.
私を見てて欲しいの よそ見しないでね
I want you to look at me, don't look away.
息をしても愛してね もっと飛べるから
Love me even as I breathe, because I can fly higher.
ナッピナッピまだまだあなたとデッカイ愛を更新中
Nappy-nappy, still updating huge love with you.
暴走しちゃったら制してね だって愛は異常主義
Control me if I go wild, because love is an extreme doctrine.
もっともっと跳ねてたいから ずっとそばで見でいてね
I want to bounce more and more, so stay right by my side.
どんな思いでも苦しいな 好きまで届くなかに
No matter what feelings, it's painful, reaching right up to love.
最大級のななななななびー
Maximum grade na-na-na-na-na-na-bee!
もっとスタイのななななななびー
More style na-na-na-na-na-na-bee!
おけおけ僕が君の神様になっちゃんよ
Okay, okay, I'll become your god!
悩み無き限界の民の皆様 けったまし時代の風の中
People of the troubled era, in the wind of the era.
自分のことさえ愛せない そんなことありませんか
Can't you even love yourself? Isn't there something like that?
誰かに認めてもらいたいな 何もうまくいかずやだよ
I want someone to acknowledge me, nothing goes well and it sucks.
神頼みふれなのに どこにいたら会えるの神様
Where can I meet you, God?
どうしたの? うんうん そっか大変だね
What's wrong? Yeah yeah, that sounds tough.
でもね 大丈夫ぜ 僕がそばでいるからさ
But you know, it's alright, because I'm right by your side.
生きてるだけで満点 自信持ちなよ全然
Just living is a perfect score, have confidence at all.
信じていいよ当然 君はとっても素敵だよ
Of course you can believe it, you are so wonderful.
ありとあらゆるこの世のすべてが 肯定! 肯定!
Everything in this world is affirmation! Affirmation!
天地全能全肯定!
Omnipotent heaven and earth, total affirmation!
それって結構かわいじゃない?
Isn't that pretty cute?
いいじゃんいいじゃんすごいじゃん いいじゃんいいじゃんえらいじゃん
That's great, that's amazing, that's impressive.
そうですそうです もっと自由に生きていいんだよ全肯定
Total affirmation that you can live more freely.
いいじゃんいいじゃんすごいじゃん いいじゃんいいじゃんえらいじゃん
That's great, that's amazing, that's impressive.
おけおけ君には最高なんだって伝えてあげる
Okay, okay, I'll tell you that you are the best.
おーけーおーけー
Okay, okay,
ぼくが君の神様になったげる
I'll become your god!
お願い！お願い！しょうがないなあ
Please! Please! You leave me no choice,
やぁやぁ、悩める人類の皆様
Hey, hey, to all troubled humanity,
けたたましい時代の只中
In the midst of a noisy era,
自分の事さえ 愛せない
unable to love even yourself—
そんなことありませんか?
Isn't that true?
「誰かに認めてもらいたいな...」
"I want someone to acknowledge me..."
「何も上手くいかずヤダヤダ」
"Nothing's going well, I hate it"
神頼みそれなのに
Even though you're praying to the gods,
どこに行ったら会えるの神様
where can I go to meet a god?
(Help me!) どうしたの~?
(Help me!) What's wrong~?
(Help me!) うんうん
(Help me!) Yeah, yeah,
(Help me!) そっか~大変だね~
(Help me!) I see~ That's tough~
(Save me!) でもね~
(Save me!) But you know~
(Save me!) 大丈夫!
(Save me!) It'll be fine!
ぼくが味方でいるからさ~
Because I'm on your side~
生きてるだけで満点
Just being alive is a perfect score,
自信持ちなよ全然
have absolute confidence!
信じていいよ当然
You can totally believe in that,
君はとっても素敵だよ!
You're so wonderful!
ありとあらゆる この世の全てを
Affirming everything in this world—
肯定! 肯定! 全知全能全肯定!
Affirmation! Affirmation! Total affirmation!
「それって結構、神じゃない?」
"Isn't that pretty much god-like?"
いい じゃん いい じゃん
It's good, it's good,
すごい じゃん
That's amazing,
いい じゃん いい じゃん えらい じゃん
it's good, it's good, you're doing great,
そう です そう です
That's right, that's right,
もっと自由に 生きていいんだよ全肯定
you can live more freely, total affirmation!
いい じゃん いい じゃん
It's good, it's good,
すごい じゃん
That's amazing,
いい じゃん いい じゃん えらい じゃん
it's good, it's good, you're doing great,
おーけーおーけー ぼくが君の
Okay, okay, I'll become your...
神様になったげる
god!
のんびりいこうよ ばっちりピカイチ
Let's take it easy, perfectly brilliant,
ファンタスティック
Fantastic!
へっちゃらポジティブ
No worries, be positive,
まぁまぁみんな無理しないでね
now everyone, don't push yourselves too hard,
めっちゃ心配だよ
I'm really worried!
もぐもぐ!
Mogu mogu!
やっぱりね!
As expected!
勇気の!
Courageous!
よし、いくぞ!
Alright, let's go!
肯定 肯定 肯定 肯定
Affirmation, affirmation, affirmation, affirmation,
全知全能 全肯定!
omni-benevolent total affirmation!
いい じゃん いい じゃん
It's good, it's good,
すごい じゃん
That's amazing,
いい じゃん いい じゃん えらい じゃん
it's good, it's good, you're doing great,
さあさあ皆様ご唱和ください!
Now, everyone, please sing along!
全知全能 全肯定!
Omni-benevolent total affirmation!
いい じゃん いい じゃん
It's good, it's good,
すごい じゃん
That's amazing,
いい じゃん いい じゃん えらい じゃん
it's good, it's good, you're doing great,
おーけーおーけー 新世界の神様になってあげる
Okay, okay, I'll become the god of the new world!
うわーー！わーー！やったー！やったー！
Wow! Yay! We did it!
うわー！すごい！
Wow! Amazing!
うわーー！すごすぎみこー！うれしそう！
Wow, that was amazing, Miko! You look so happy!
ということで皆さん、ホロライブ4thフェス Our Bright Paradeデイ1始まりました！イエーイ！
So everyone, Hololive 4th Fes "Our Bright Parade" Day 1 has begun! Yay!
いや自己紹介してきましたね！皆さん！
We just did our self-introductions, everyone!
今後キズネ…噛んだキズネ…噛んだアンドハイプレンズ！
From now on, Kizune... I tripped over my words... Kizune... I tripped, and Hi-Friends!
ホロライブ1期生 げまーず 白上フブキです！
I'm Shirakami Fubuki from Hololive 1st Gen / Gamers!
そして！ぺこぺこ！
And! Peko-peko!
ぺこぺこぺこぺこ、ホロライブ3期生のうさだ…ぺこらぺこー！
Peko-peko peko-peko, Hololive 3rd Gen Usada... Pekora-peko!
ど緊張。どうしよう。めちゃめちゃ緊張したね。
Super nervous. What should I do? We were so nervous.
忘れちゃいめことか、忘れちゃいめことか、めっ…間違えちゃいめことか。
Forgetting things, forgetting things, making mistakes...
まあでもさっきね、ソロで歌いましたけど緊張したもんね。
Well, we sang solo earlier, but we were so nervous.
緊張したぺこよー。でもね、皆さん盛り上がってました！盛り上がってくれたぺこねー！
I was so nervous, peko. But everyone was getting into it! They cheered for us, peko!
いいね！あっ配信組の皆もほんとにね、ありがとーー！いやー盛り上がってくれてて。ありがとーー！
Nice! Ah, to everyone watching the stream too, thank you so much! Yay, thanks for getting hyped. Thank you!
いや、そうだぺこちゃん。やっぱさ、ライブと言ったらさ、コーレスポンスなんだけどさ、ぺこちゃんやりたかったぺこらも、そうやりたかったーって言ってたじゃん。コーレスポンスやってほしいんだよね。
Yeah, that's right, Peko-chan. You know, when you think of a live show, there's call-and-response, and Pekora, you said you wanted to do call-and-response too, right? You wanted to do it.
あ、あれ、あれ。どんどん、どんどん。あれをちょっとやりたくて。あのぺこらの挨拶のあれですな。そうあれだあれ。ちょっと白上もおまーじゅしてやりたいんですけども、まずはちょっとやっぱりぺこちゃんのね、みんなもね、言いたいですもんね。
Ah, that, that. Gradually, gradually. I wanted to do that a bit. That greeting of Pekora's. Yes, that one. Shirakami wants to pay homage to it too, but first, of course, everyone wants to say Peko-chan's too, right?
まあ、皆さん分かってますよね。あれですよね、ぺこらが言ったらみんながぺこちゃーんって。そうぺこちゃーんって。ぺこちゃんなんですよ。分かりましたか？いきますよ。はい。じゃあいきますよ。
Well, everyone knows it, right? It's that, when Pekora says it, everyone says "Peko-chan!" Yes, "Peko-chan!" It's Peko-chan. Do you understand? Here we go. Yes. Then here we go.
どどんがどんがどん！全VTuber中超絶可愛いのは誰だ！？どどんがどんがどん！ペコちゃーん！
Dodon ga don ga don! Who is the cutest among all VTubers?! Dodon ga don ga don! Peko-chan!
いやあ、すごい！すごい！ありがとー！
Wow, amazing! Amazing! Thank you!
じゃあちょっと白上也やらさていただきます。ふぶちゃんバージョンがあるみたいぺこなのでお願いします。ふぶちゃんなんですからね、いきましょう。
Well then, I'll let Shirakami do it too. It seems there's a Fubuki version, so please go ahead. Since it's Fubuki-chan, let's go.
ここコンコンコン！全VTuber中可愛いキツネは誰だ！？
Koko-kon-kon-kon! Who is the cutest fox among all VTubers?!
こんこんこんこんこん！
Kon-kon-kon-kon-kon!
へべっだー！
Hey guys!
すごねこらね、使っていっていいことですからね。
Pekora, it's amazing that you can use that.
いやでも本当にこんこんこんこんこん！
No, really, kon-kon-kon-kon-kon!
いいね！
Nice!
めちゃめちゃいいと！やった！
That's super good! Yay!
こんこんこんこんこん！
Kon-kon-kon-kon-kon!
やった！はい！
Yay! Yes!
お、なんでぺこちゃん？
Oh, why, Peko-chan?
ペコらはもっとやりたいのがの
Pekora wants to do more of
ふぶちゃんのさ、なんか何百回愛してるみたいな
Fubuki's, like, 'I love you' hundreds of times...
あーなんかその、それのペコらも
Ah, like that, Pekora also wants to...
やりたいよペコちゃん！やりたいやりたいやりたい！
Want to do it, Peko-chan! Want to do it, want to do it!
やっと白髪がのお手本見せてますね。
Finally, Shirakami is showing an example.
じゃあ白髪が、白髪の事を何万回好きって言ったら皆さん答えるの分かりますよね？
So if Shirakami says 'How much do you love Shirakami?' you know how to answer, right?
わかんないから。言ってください。できますよ！
We don't know. Please say it. You can do it!
白髪の事を何万回好き？
How many tens of thousands of times do you love Shirakami?
100万回愛してるよー！
I love you a million times!
よかった！よかった！
Yay! Yay!
好きって言ったらね、ちゃんと愛してって返してくれるんですよ。
When I say 'I love you', you reply by saying 'I love you' back.
じゃあぺこらも、それ答えてくれるのかな？
Well then, will Pekora answer that too?
あ、ちょっと、答えるしかないな。準備。
Ah, wait, I have no choice but to answer. Get ready.
おし！スイングとかして、ぺこちゃんお願いします。
Alright! Let's swing, Peko-chan, please.
はい、じゃあみんなも準備いいぺこだね！ぺこらのこと何万回好き？
Okay, so everyone's got their Peko-ready readiness! How many tens of thousands of times do you love Pekora?
100万回愛してるよー！
I love you a million times!
いや、いいよね、やっぱね！
Man, it's great, as expected!
声が出すってね、本当に今日気持ちいい！
Being able to use your voice feels really amazing today!
最高ぺこらです！ありがとうございます！
Pekora is at her peak! Thank you very much!
ありがとう、みんな！
Thank you, everyone!
さてさて、まず一曲揃ってね、終わりましたけども。
Now then, we've finished our first song together.
改めて歌ってみてどうでした？
How was it singing it again?
いやー、ぺこらはもう、満身創痍というか
Man, Pekora is already completely exhausted...
いや、本当に！
No, really!
なんか、いや、もうみんなが目の前にいてね、こうやってハァ、ハァとかやりながらもう、なんかもう感動だし緊張もあるぺこだけど、なんかもう楽しい、本当に楽しみで、ありがとね、今日本当に！
Like, everyone was right in front of me, panting like this, it's so moving and yet nerve-wracking, but it's so much fun, I'm really looking forward to it, thank you so much today!
まだまだこれからだけど！
There's still more to come!
そうだよ、まだまだこれからだけどね。もう白金のみんなの声ちゃんと聞こえてたぞ、ありがと！
That's right, there's still more to come. We could hear everyone's voices loud and clear, thank you!
ぺこちゃんは、ぺこちゃんは？
Peko-chan, Peko-chan?
え、もう本当に楽しかった！トップバッターだったんだけど今回は
Uh, I really had fun! I was the first batter this time, but
そうだよね、そう。なんかね、スーパー白金タイプと
That's right. Like, super Shirakami type and...
ペコだったよ！いや本当にありがとう！
It was Peko! Thank you so much!
さてさて、今回のハッシュタグなんですけど、皆さんわかってますよね？
Now then, as for this time's hashtag, you all know it, right?
分かってるぺこでしょー！
Of course you know, Peko!
ハッシュタグ「ホロライブDAY2」です！
The hashtag is #HololiveDay2!
こちらいっぱい呟いてください！ぜひぜひスクショも
Please tweet a lot with this! Please, please take screenshots too.
ぜひぜひスクショもぜひぜひお願いします！
Please, please take screenshots!
そしてなんと悲しいお知らせです。え？
And what a sad announcement. Eh?
YouTubeでご覧の皆さんはここまでとなります。
To everyone watching on YouTube, this is where we part.
まだまだ一緒にみんなで盛り上がっていきたいのでぜひ
We want to keep getting hyped together with everyone, so please
概要欄から配信サイトへ！
Go to the streaming site from the description box!
ということでまだまだね、これからも盛り上がっていきますので
So with that, we'll keep getting more and more hyped, so
締めのご挨拶いきますか！
Shall we go with our closing greeting?
いきましょう！
Let's go!
せーの！広がる
Ready, go! Spreading out
ハライブ！
Our Bright Parade!
(Music / Cheers)
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part has ended! Thank you for watching!